

Zhijie Wei

Profile

I am an undergraduate in Software Engineering and Management at University of Gothenburg in 2022.

- I am careful, resistant to stress, self-motivated with a strong desire to learn new things and like to take my own initiative.
- I am active, like to cooperate in teamwork for a positive working environment with other colleagues.
- I am open to new ideas and like to listen to advice from experienced colleagues.
- I am looking forward to new challenges and I am convinced that my competence and positive attitude are my biggest advantages and I want to contribute what I can to the company.

★ Personal projects

Big data COVID-19 analysis

June 2022 — October 2022

Big data analysis of COVID-19 epidemic worldwide through daily data which ranged from January 2020 to March 2021 from Johns Hopkins University. Through using pandas and pyecharts, it visualizes how much and fast this epidemic spreads around the world.

10 data analysis exercises

August 2021 — June 2022

10 very popular data analysis exercises I have practised with jupyter notebook in my spare time, including Iris flowers, Titanic, K means clustering, linnear regression and logistic regression etc.

Pizza ordering system

March 2022 — June 2022

An exercise of ordering pizza online using Vue-cli and element UI and webpack. Users can browse different kinds of pizza, their prices, add to cart, generate and submit orders.

Deep learning stock price prediction

November 2021 — January 2022

A system that uses deep neural network(DNN) model to predict the price increase or decrease of one or more stocks for the next month. It includes technologies such as anaconda, tensorflow, keras, python, Django framework etc.

Education

Bachelor of Science within major in Software Engineering and Management, University of Gothenburg, Gothenburg

September 2019 — June 2022

- Experience in an Agile/Scrum development process
- Basic knowledge of testing, software quality assurance and DevOps
- Experience of CI/CD tools: GitLab

Details

Mölndal, 43161 Sweden zjwei0201@gmail.com

Links

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ zhijie-wei-858895219/ Personal GitHub: https://github.com/ZJW-92

Skills

Jupyter notebook

Tableau Python

R

SQL MySQL

Machine Learning

Robot Framework

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Java

С

C++

Vue

React

Microsoft Excel

Languages

Chinese

English

Swedish

- Basic database knowledge: MySQL, MongoDB
- Machine Learning and Deep Learning practice with jupyter notebook and python
- Basic applicable development languages: Java, JavaScript, Python.
- Basic web application frontend and framework (e.g. React, Vue) and backend framework (e.g. Django)
- Solid mathematics background: Calculus, Linear algebra etc

Hermods AB, Gothenburg

December 2019 — May 2020

Passed svenska som andraspråk 2.

Grade: C

Studium, Gothenburg

September 2018 — December 2019

Passed SFI D and svenska som andraspråk 1

Grade: B, E

Master, Shanghai University of Science and Technology, Shanghai

September 2014 — June 2017

Master degree of Industrial Economics with specializing in SPSS statistical tool.

Exchange student, Högskolan i Borås, Borås

September 2015 — June 2016

Courses: International management, Supply Chain Management and Basic Swedish I and II.

Experience

Chinese to English translator at Shanghai Xinzhi Private Entry-Exit Service Co., Ltd., Shanghai

June 2017 — June 2018

 Organize customers' immigration documents, translate to English and proofread.

Volunteer at Swedish Red Cross, Borås

April 2016 — June 2016

 Move second-hand books, clothes to the warehouse and responsible for cashier.

Financial Assistant at Shanghai Ouhong Asset Management Co., Ltd., Shanghai

January 2014 — June 2014

Review financial documents and organize files, and manage invoices.